A Guide to the Papers of the Tucker, Harrison and Smith Families, 1790-1940
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Mary Stuart Harrison to Francis H. Smith ca. 1852, AL, ALS (Box 9)
- Edward B. Smith to Summerfield Smith 1853 Jan. 2, ALS (Box 9)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1853 Jan. 3, ALS (Box 9)
- Mary F. Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1853 Jan. 7, ALS (Box 9)
- Margaret Harrison Stevens to [Mary Jane Harrison] 1853 Jan. 15, ALS (Box 9)
- Fannie M. Stuart (Mrs. J. C. Wallace) to Caroline E. Harrison 1853 Jan. 17, ALS (Box 9)
- Margaret H. Stevens to Mary S. Harrison (Mrs. Peachey Harrison) 1853 Jan. 21, ALS (Box 9)
- Matthew G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1853 Feb. 2, ALS (Box 9)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1853 Feb. 11, ALS (Box 9)
- Fannie M. Stuart (Mrs. J. C. Wallace) to Margaret Harrison Stevens 1853 Feb. 14, ALS (Box 9)
- Matthew G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1853 Feb. 16, ALS (Box 9)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison 1853 Feb. 25, ALS (Box 9)
- Gessner Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1853 Feb. 26, ALS (Box 9)
- Mary F. Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1853 Feb. 26, ALS (Box 9)
- Professor William B. Rogers to Professor E. H. Smith 1853 Feb. 27, ALS (Box 9)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1853 March 14, ALS (Box 9)
- M. T. C. to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1853 March 17, ALS (Box 9)
- Matthew G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith [1853?] March 22, ALS (Box 9)
- Gessner Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison 1853 March 23, ALS (Box 9)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1853 March 24, ALS (Box 9)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1853 April 2, ALS (Box 9)
- Gessner Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1853 April 10, ALS (Box 9)
- Matthew G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1853 April 13, ALS (Box 9)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1853 April 15, ALS (Box 9)
- Matthew G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1853 April 25, ALS (Box 9)
- Francis H. Smith to Mary Stuart Harrison 1853 April 29, ALS (Box 9)
- Gessner Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1853 May 2, ALS (Box 9)
- Francis H. Smith to Mary Stuart Harrison 1853 May 2, ALS (Box 9)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1853 May 4, ALS (Box 9)
- Francis H. Smith to Mary Stuart Harrison 1853 May 6 & 13, ALS (Box 9)
- Matthew G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1853 May 16, ALS (Box 9)
- Gessner Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison 1853 May 22, ALS (Box 9)
- George Tucker to Maria R. F. (Tucker) Rives 1853 May 29, ALS (Box 9)
- Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus to John A. Broadus 1853 June 4, ALS (Box 9)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1853 June 6, ALS (Box 9)
- Mary Stuart Harrison to [Francis Stuart] 1853 June 10, ALS (Box 9)
- Gessner Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison 1853 June 11, ALS (Box 9)
- Dr. John Johnston to Francis H. Smith 1853 June 15, ALS (Box 9)
- Matthew G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1853 June 17, ALS (Box 9)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1853 June 17 & 20, 2 ALS (Box 9)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1853 June 20, ALS (Box 9)
- William G. Stevens to Francis H. Smith 1853 June 23, ALS (Box 9)
- General Asa Rogers to Francis H. Smith 1853 June 24, ALS (Box 9)
- Daniel G. Smith to Franics H. Smith 1853 July 4, ALS (Box 9)
- R. T. W. Duke to Francis H. Smith appointing him Professor of Natural Philosophy at University of Virginia 1853 July 6, ALS (Box 9)
- George Tucker Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1853 July 7, ALS (Box 9)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1853 July 8, ALS (Box 9)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1854 July 9, ALS (Box 9)
- Matthew G. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1853 July 22, ALS (Box 9)
- Matthew G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1853 Aug. 12, ALS (Box 9)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1853 Aug. 19, 22 & 28, 3 ALS (Box 9)
- Matthew G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1853 Sept. 1, ALS (Box 9)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith (Mrs. Francis H. Smith) to Ellen E. Smith (Mrs. Daniel G. Smith) 1853 Sept. 3, ALS (Box 9)
- Edgar Garth to Edward T. Harrison 1853 Sept. 4, ALS (Box 9)
- William B. Rogers to Francis H. Smith 1853 Sept. 10, ALS (Box 9)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1853 Sept. 10 & 12, 2 ALS (Box 9)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1853 Sept. 13, ALS (Box 9)
- Anna M. Smith to Ellen E. Smith 1853 Sept. 16, ALS (Box 9)
- Gessner Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1853 Sept. 17, ALS (Box 9)
- John C. Stockton to Edward T. Harrison 1853 Sept. 17, ALS (Box 9)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1853 Sept. 20, ALS (Box 9)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1853 Sept. 24, ALS (Box 9)
- Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith to Ellen E. Smith 1853 Oct. 3, ALS (Box 9)
- Matthew G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1853 Oct. 4, ALS (Box 9)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1853 Oct. 8, ALS (Box 9)
- Gessner Harrison to Professor W. G. Cross 1853 Oct. 10, ALS (Box 9)
- Mary Stuart Smith to [Daniel G. Smith] 1853 Oct. 10, ALS (Box 9)
- Matthew G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1853 Oct. 11, ALS (Box 9)
- William B. Rogers to Francis H. Smith 1853 Oct. 11, ALS (Box 9)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis and Edward Smith 1853 Oct. 11, ALS (Box 9)
- Matthew G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1853 Nov. 2, ALS (Box 9)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1853 Nov. 4, ALS (Box 9)
- Gessner Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1853 Nov. 10, ALS (Box 9)
- William B. Rogers to Francis H. Smith 1853 Nov. 11, ALS (Box 9)
- Mary Stuart Smith to [Margaret F. Harrison Stevens] ca. 1853 Nov. 16, ALS (Box 9)
- Matthew G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1853 Nov. 17, ALS (Box 9)
- Mary Stuart Smith to [Ellen Hamilton Smith] [1853] Nov. 18, ALS (Box 9)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1853 Dec. 5, ALS (Box 9)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1853 Dec. 5, ALS (Box 9)
- Matthew G. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1853 Dec. 7, ALS (Box 9)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Daniel G. Smith 1853 Dec. 7, ALS (Box 9)
- Matthew G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1853 Dec. 9, ALS (Box 9)
- (signiture torn away) Maria C. Broadus to Mary Stuart Smith [1853] Dec. 13, AL (Box 9)
- William B. Rogers to Francis H. Smith 1853 Dec. 20, ALS (Box 10)
- Matthew G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1853 Dec. 21, ALS (Box 10)
- Gessner Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison 1853 Dec. 21, ALS (Box 10)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1853 Dec. 24, 2 ALS (Box 10)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1853 Dec. 24, ALS (Box 10)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Francis H. Smith 1853 Dec. 25, ALS (Box 10)
- Francis H. Smith to Mary Stuart (Harrison) Smith 1853 Dec. 26 & 27, ALS (Box 10)
- Mary J. Jannison to Eliza T. Harrison (Mrs. Gessner Harrison) [1853], ALS (Box 10)
- Matthew G. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1854 Jan. 6, ALS (Box 10)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1854 Jan. 7, ALS (Box 10)
- Edward B. Smith to Daniel G. Smith 1854 Jan. 9, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1854 Jan. 12, ALS (Box 10)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison [1854 Jan. 13], ALS (Box 10)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1854 Jan. 17, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1854 Jan. 19 & 24, 2 ALS (Box 10)
- Mary F. Harrison to Margaret Harrison [1854] Jan., ALS (Box 10)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1854 Feb. 4, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1854 Feb. 9, ALS (Box 10)
- Gessner Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1854 Feb. 13, ALS (Box 10)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1854 Feb. 14, ALS (Box 10)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1854 Feb. 18, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1854 Feb. 20, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Daniel G. Smith 1854 March 1, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1854 March 1, ALS (Box 10)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1854 March 6 & 13, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1854 March 17, ALS (Box 10)
- Gessner Harrison to [?] 1854 March 21, ALS (Box 10)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1854 March 24, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1854 April 4, ALS (Box 10)
- Jacob R. Stevens to William G. Stevens 1854 April 7, ALS (Box 10)
- William G. Stevens to Margaret F. Stevens 1854 April 14, ALS (Box 10)
- Mary F. Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1854 April 22, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1854 April 24, ALS (Box 10)
- D. S. Harding to Mr. And Mrs. Daniel Smith [1854] May 1, ALS (Box 10)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1854 May 2, ALS (Box 10)
- Gessner Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1854 May 7, ALS (Box 10)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1854 May 8, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1854 June 5, ALS (Box 10)
- Gessner Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison 1854 June 11, ALS (Box 10)
- Gessner Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1854 July 7, ALS (Box 10)
- Mary S. (Harrison) Smith to sister Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1854 July 11, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1854 Aug. 1, ALS (Box 10)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Gessner Harrison 1854 Aug. 21, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1854 Aug. 23, ALS (Box 10)
- M. R. Paine to Caroline E. Harrison 1854 Sept. 7, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1854 Sept. 20, ALS (Box 10)
- H. V. Davis to Daniel G. Smith 1854 Oct. 10, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1854 Oct. 11, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1854 Oct. 17, ALS (Box 10)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1854 Oct. 25, ALS (Box 10)
- George T. Harrison to sister Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1854 Nov. 14, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1854 Nov. 16, ALS (Box 10)
- Mary F. Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1854 Nov. 19, ALS (Box 10)
- H. H. Worthington to Dr. Gessner Harrison 1854 Nov. 21, ALS (Box 10)
- Mary E. (Rodes) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1854 Dec. 6, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1854 Dec. 12, ALS (Box 10)
- Thomas Goode Tucker to Gessner Harrison 1854 Dec. 17, ALS (Box 10)
- Mary F. Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1854 Dec. 28, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1854 Dec. 29, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith [1854?], ALS (Box 10)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1855 Jan. 12, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1855 Jan. 17, ALS (Box 10)
- Fannie M. Stuart (Mrs. J. C. Wallace) to Mary Jane Harrison 1855 Jan. 24, ALS (Box 10)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1855 Feb. 1, ALS (Box 10)
- Mary M. Broadus to Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1855 Feb. 2, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1855 Feb. 14, AL(fragment) (Box 10)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1855 Feb. 22, ALS (Box 10)
- Mary F. Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1855 Feb., ALS (Box 10)
- Fannie M. Stuart Wallace to Mary Jane Harrison 1855 March 6, ALS (Box 10)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Dr. Gessner Harrison 1855 March 27, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1855 April 2, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1855 April 18, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1855 April 23; May 12, ALS (Box 10)
- George W. Green to Daniel G. Smith 1855 May 16, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1855 May 17, ALS (Box 10)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1855 May 18, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1855 May 21, ALS (Box 10)
- James L. Hamilton and his wife to Ellen E. (Hamilton) Smith 1855 May 30, ALS (Box 10)
- Gessner Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison 1855 June 3 & 10, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1855 June 18, ALS (Box 10)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1855 June 22, ALS (Box 10)
- George W. Green to Daniel G. Smith 1855 June 25, ALS (Box 10)
- Daniel G. Smith to Howard Smith 1855 July 11, ALS (Box 10)
- Francis H. Smith to Mary Stuart Smith 1855 July 11, ALS (Box 10)
- George W. Green to Daniel G. Smith 1855 July 19, ALS (Box 10)
- Francis H. Smith to Mary Stuart Smith 1855 July 19, ALS (Box 10)
- James Pleasants to Professor Francis H. Smith 1855 July 20, ALS (Box 10)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza Tucker Harrison 1855 July 25, ALS (Box 10)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1855 July 25, ALS (Box 10)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1855 July 29, ALS (Box 10)
- George W. Green to Daniel G. Smith 1855 July, ALS (Box 10)
- Mary Stuart Harrison to Francis H. Smith 1855 Aug. 1, ALS (Box 10)
- Francis H. Smith to Mary Stuart Smith 1855 Aug. 3-16, 5 ALS (Box 10)
- M. A. Cabell to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1855 Sept. 3, ALS (Box 10)
- Maria C. Broadus to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1855 Sept. 5, ALS (Box 10)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison (Mrs. Gessner Harrison) 1855 Sept. 5, ALS (Box 10)
- George W. Green to Daniel G. Smith 1855 Sept. 6, ALS (Box 11)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1855 Sept. 7, ALS (Box 11)
- [?] Nash to Edward T. Harrison 1855 Sept. 27, ALS (Box 11)
- George W. Green to Daniel G. Smith 1855 Sept. 28, ALS (Box 11)
- George Tucker and L> A. T. to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1855 Oct. 6, ALS (Box 11)
- George W. Green to Daniel G. Smith 1855 Oct. 10, ALS (Box 11)
- Mary F. Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1855 Oct. 12, ALS (Box 11)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1855 Oct. 15, ALS (Box 11)
- H. M. Smith to [?] 1855 Oct. 21, ALS (Box 11)
- George W. Green to Daniel G. Smith 1855 Oct. 24, ALS (Box 11)
- Mary Jane Harrison to niece Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1855 Oct. 24, ALS (Box 11)
- Henrietta McGuffey to Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1855 Nov. 1, ALS (Box 11)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1855 Nov. 17, ALS (Box 11)
- Lillie [Hamilton] to Ellen E. Smith 1855 Nov. 17, ALS (Box 11)
- Daniel G. Smith to Summerfield Smith 1855 Nov. 19, ALS (Box 11)
- Gessner Hamilton to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1855 Nov. 28, ALS (Box 11)
- Allen B. Magruder to Francis H. Smith 1855 Nov. 30, ALS (Box 11)
- George W. Green to Daniel G. Smith 1855 Dec. 25, ALS (Box 11)
- Wiliam G. Stevens to Margaret F. Stevens [1855?], ALS (Box 11)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1956 Jan. 1, ALS (Box 11)
- William G. Stevens to Margaret F. Stevens [1856 Jan. 10?], ALS (Box 11)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1856 Jan. 14, ALS (Box 11)
- Mary F. Harrison to Eliza T. Harrison 1856 Jan. 21, ALS (Box 11)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives and her husband to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1856 Jan. 28, ALS (Box 11)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1856 Jan. 30, ALS (Box 11)
- George W. Green to Daniel G. Smith 1856 Feb. 15, 20, 28, March 13, April 1, 22, June 16, Aug. 8, 25, Sept. 13 & 21, 11 ALS (Box 11)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1856 Feb. 23, ALS (Box 11)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1856 Feb. 29, ALS (Box 11)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1856 March 2 & 6, ALS (Box 11)
- Daniel G. Smith to Francis H. Smith 1856 March 22, ALS (Box 11)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1856 March 26, ALS (Box 11)
- Alexander G. Smith to Daniel G. Smith 1856 March, ALS (Box 11)
- Alexander G. Smith to Daniel G. Smith 1856 April 8, ALS (Box 11)
- Gessner Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison 1856 April 12, ALS (Box 11)
- William G. Stevens to Margaret F. Stevens [1856?] April 13, ALS (Box 11)
- William G. Stevens to Margaret F. Stevens 1856 April 16, ALS (Box 11)
- Gessner Harrison to mother Mrs. Peachey Harrison 1856 April 27, ALS (Box 11)
- William G. Stevens to Williette Stevens 1856 April 28, ALS (Box 11)
- William G. Stevens to Williette Stevens 1856 May 4 & 8, 2 ALS (Box 11)
- Gessner Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison 1856 May 11, ALS (Box 11)
- William G. Stevens to Margaret F. Stevens 1856 May 21 & 22, 2 ALS (Box 11)
- Gessner Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison 1856 June 1, ALS (Box 11)
- E. F. Douglas to Maria (Tucker) Rives 1856 June 3, ALS (Box 11)
- Henrietta McGuffey to Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1856 June 7-Nov. 11, 3 ALS (Box 11)
- Eliza T. Harrison to Mary J. Harrison 1856 June 9, ALS (Box 11)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1856 June 16, ALS (Box 11)
- Alexander G. Smith to Daniel G. Smith 1856 June 29, ALS (Box 11)
- George Tucker to Gessner Harrison 1856 June 30, ALS (Box 11)
- Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison (Mrs. Gessner Harrison) to Mary Stuart and Francis Smith [1956] July 21, ALS (Box 11)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1856 July 23, ALS (Box 11)
- Maria R. Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1856 July 24, ALS (Box 11)
- Maria R. Rives to niece, Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1856 July 28, ALS (Box 11)
- Gessner Harrison to Edward T. Harrison 1856 July 29, ALS (Box 11)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1856 Aug. 1, ALS (Box 11)
- Daniel G. Smith to J. Howard Smith 1856 Aug. 11, 23, & Sept. 6, ALS (Box 11)
- Alexander G. Smith to Daniel G. Smith 1856 Aug. 13, ALS (Box 11)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1856 Aug. 14, ALS (Box 11)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1856 Aug. 15, ALS (Box 11)
- Edward Tiffin Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1856 Aug. 16, ALS (Box 11)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Edward T. Harrison 1856 Aug. 24, ALS (Box 11)
- Maria C. Broadus to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1856 Aug. 25, ALS (Box 11)
- Eliza L. C. Harrison to daughter Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1856 Aug. 25, ALS (Box 11)
- Daniel G. Smith to Howard Smith 1856 Aug. 25, ALS (Box 11)
- H. Shaffner to [Daniel G. Smith] 1856 Aug. 29, ALS (Box 11)
- Eliza T. Harrison to Mary J. Harrison 1856 Sept. 29, ALS (Box 11)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1856 Oct. 13, ALS (Box 11)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison (Mrs. Gessner Harrison) 1856 Oct. 28, ALS (Box 11)
- [George Tucker Harrison] to Edward T. Harrison 1856 Nov. 5, AL (Box 11)
- Eliza C. Broadus to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1856 Nov. 8, ALS (Box 11)
- Eliza (Tukcer) Harrison to Mary F. Harrison 1856 Nov. 24, ALS (Box 11)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1856 Dec. 2, ALS (Box 11)
- Augustus G. Smith to Daniel G. Smith 1856 Dec. 10, ALS (Box 11)
- George Tucker Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1856 Dec. 11, ALS (Box 11)
- William G. Stevens to Margaret F. Stevens [1857?] Dec. 18, ALS (Box 11)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Hamilton 1856 Dec. 28, ALS (Box 11)
- George Tucker Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1856 Dec. 25, ALS (Box 11)
- Daniel G. Smith to William S. Walker [ ca. 1856], AL (Box 11)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison [1856], ALS (Box 11)
- Maira (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1857 Jan. 2; Jan. 23; April 2; May 6; July 20, 25, 31; Aug. 5; Sept. 8, 23; Oct. 21; Nov. 23; Dec. 7, 13 ALS (Box 11)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary F. Harrison 1857 Jan. & Sept. 28, ALS (Box 11)
- George Tucker Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1857 Jan. 16 & Feb. 11, 2 ALS (Box 11)
- Lillie R. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1857 Jan. 30, ALS (Box 11)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1857 Jan. 30; March 9; April 19; May 18; June 16; July 9; Nov. 5, 7 ALS (Box 11)
- Eliza (Tucker) Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1857 Feb. 9 & 20; Oct. 26; Dec. 17, 4 ALS (Box 11)
- Henry William Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1857 March 23, ALS (Box 11)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1857 April 2; Oct. 6 & 24; Dec. 9, 4 ALS (Box 11)
- Maria C. Broadus to Eliza (Tucker) 1857 April 16; June 6; July 28 & 30; Aug. 8, ALS (Box 11)
- Charles Carter Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1857 April; May 31; June 12, ALS (Box 11)
- Jacob R. Stevens to William G. Stevens 1857 April 8, ALS (Box 11)
- Gessner Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1857 April 27 & July 21, 2 ALS (Box 11)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Rosalie Rives 1857 May 23, ALS (Box 11)
- George W. Green to Daniel G. Smith 1857 May 26; July 7; Oct. 7; Dec. 14 & 23, 5 ALS (Box 12)
- George Tucker Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1857 July & Sept. 11, 2 ALS (Box 12)
- George Rives to Daniel Grove Smith 1857 May, ALS (Box 12)
- Charles Carter Harrison to Edward Tiffin Harrison 1857 June 7, ALS (Box 12)
- Mary F. Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1857 June 9; Aug. 28; Sept. 2, 5, 9, 29; Nov. 2, 6 ALS, 1 AL (Box 12)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1857 July 6, ALS (Box 12)
- Eleanor Rosalie Harrison and Maria Rives (Mrs. W. M. Thornton) to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1857 July 7, ALS (Box 12)
- Francis H. Smith to Mary Stuart Smith 1857 July 12; Sept. 26; Oct. 12, 13, & 16, 6 ALS (Box 12)
- Maria C. Broadus to Lida (Eliza) Broadus 1857 July 13, ALS (Box 12)
- Fannie M. Stuart (Mrs. J. C. Wallace) to Mary Jane Harrison 1857 July 24, ALS (Box 12)
- Fannie M. Stuart (MRs. J. C. Wallace) to [Caroline E. Harrison] 1857 Aug. 4 & Sept. 22, 2 ALS (Box 12)
- Frances E. Gwathmey (Frances Fielding Lewis) to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1857 Aug. 8 & Oct. 29, 2 ALS (Box 12)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Mary Stuart Smith 1857 Aug. 11, ALS (Box 12)
- Eliza L. C. Harrison to Maria C. (Harrison) Broadus 1857 Aug. 14, ALS (Box 12)
- Augustus G. Smith to Daniel G. Smith 1857 Aug. 15, ALS (Box 12)
- Addie Rodes to [Caroline E. Harrison] 1857 Aug. 17, ALS (Box 12)
- Gessner Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1857 Aug. 24, ALS (Box 12)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Dr. Gessner Harrison 1857 Aug. 25, ALS (Box 12)
- Gessner Harrison to [?] 1857 Sept. 3, ALS (Box 12)
- Gessner Harrison to Edward T. Harrison 1857 Sept. 3 & 4, 2 ALS (Box 12)
- Mary C. Broadus to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1857 Sept. 5, 8, 11, 14, 19, 5 ALS (Box 12)
- Mary F. Harrison to Mary (Stewart) Harrison 1857 Sept. 7, ALS (Box 12)
- Peachey Gessner Harrison to Summerfield [?] 1857 Sept. 11, ALS (Box 12)
- William G. Stevens to Margaret F. Stevens 1857 Sept. 11 & 25, ALS (Box 12)
- George Tucker Harrison to Eliza Tiffin Harrison 1857 Sept. 16, ALS (Box 12)
- Maria C. Broadus to Mary Stuart Smith 1857 Sept. 17, ALS (Box 12)
- Mary F. Harrision to Margaret Harrison Stevens 1857 Sept. 24, ALS (Box 12)
- Maria Rives to Mary Stuart Smith (her niece) 1857 Sept. 24, ALS (Box 12)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Francis H. Smith 1857 Oct. 7, 14, & 20, 3 ALS (Box 12)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Eliza T. Harrison 1857 Oct. 14, ALS (Box 12)
- Henrietta Hepburn to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1857 Oct. 21, ALS (Box 12)
- George Tucker Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1857 Nov. 13; Dec. 2 & 24, 3 ALS (Box 12)
- Charles Carter Harrison to Dr. Gessner Harrison, ALS (Box 12)
- Business letters of Daniel G. Smith 1857, 8 items (Box 12)
- Mary Jane Harrison to Caroline E. Harrison ca. 1857, ALS(fragment) (Box 12)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison [1857], ALS (Box 12)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Mary Stuart Smith [1857?], ALS (Box 12)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Mary (Stewart) Harrison [1857], ALS(fragment) (Box 12)
- Mary Stuart Smith to Daniel G. Smith ca. 1857, ALS (Box 12)
- Augustus G. Smith to Daniel G. Smith 1858 Jan. 7, ALS (Box 12)
- Maria (Tucker) Rives to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1858 Jan. 11; Feb. 18 & 24; March 2, 7, & 9; April 28; May 15 & 26; June 12; Aug. 19, 11 ALS (Box 12)
- Gessner Harrison to Mary Jane Harrison 1858 Jan. 13, ALS (Box 12)
- Mary F. Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1858 Jan. 14, ALS (Box 12)
- George Tucker Harrison to Eliza (Tucker) Harrison 1858 Jan. 18; Feb. 2 & 21; June 5 & 19; July 12, 6 ALS (Box 12)
- Rev. Samuel Rodgers to Daniel G. Smith 1858 Jan. 18 & 29, 2 ALS (Box 12)
- Eliza P. Hamilton to Ellen E. Smith 1858 Jan. 21; Feb. 6; March 5; April 14; July 5 & 17; Aug. 23; Sept. 10; Dec. 13, 6 ALS, 3 AL(fragment) (Box 12)
- George W. Green to Daniel G. Smith 1858 Jan. 27; March 15 & 29; April 13; May 31; July 9; Aug. 28, Oct. 25, 9 ALS (Box 12)
- Business letters of Daniel G. Smith 1858 Feb. 1 & 4, 2 items (Box 12)
- William G. Stevens to Williette Stevens 1858 Feb. 2, ALS (Box 12)
- George Tucker to Eliza L. C. (Tucker) Harrison 1858 Feb. 3 & 27; March 9 & 23; April 17; May 17; Nov. 9 & 27, 8 ALS (Box 12)